

EZEQUIEL DEL VITTO

FRONTEND DEVELOPER CERTIFIED TRANSLATOR (EN<>SPA)

ABOUT ME

My name is Ezequiel and I am a freelance Frontend Developer. My stack is HTML5, CSS3, Javascript and React.

I am also a Certified Translator with over 6 years of translation and proofreading experience. I can guarantee high-quality professional results.

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Javascript
- React
- EN <> SPA translations

CONTACT

E-mail: delvittoezequiel@gmail.com Mobile number; (+54) 11-5802-2188 Residence: Buenos Aires, Argentina

JOB EXPERIENCE

CERTIFIED TRANSLATIONS | FREELANCER

NOV 2018 - PRESENT

- Translation of official documents
- Translation of academic documents
- Subtitling
- Proofreading

PRIVATE ENGLISH TEACHER

APRIL 2015 - DECEMBER 2020

- International exams preparation
- Essay composition
- Speaking and fluency

EDUCATION

COURSEIT - PROGRAMMING SCHOOL

NOVEMBER 2020 - JULY 2021

Frontend course

UNIVERSIDAD DEL MUSEO SOCIAL ARGENTINO

MARCH 2012 - NOVEMBER 2018

- English Certified Translator (2012-2018)
- Certified Court Interpreter (2016 2018)
- Literary and non-literary translator (2012 - 2015)